Th-This really is really
cramped for two people.
It is.
I have to say, those two...
Yuri-tan.
Masa-tan.
Smooch!
We're trapped in a very
sticky situation right now!
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#09 He Wants to Talk Privately...
Smooch!
As for how we ended up here...
Meowtaro merchandise from 30 years ago?
Right.
It's for the upcoming Meowtaro
30th anniversary exhibit.
It should be in storage in the basement
Could you go look for it?
Sure thing.
It might be a bit much to do on your own,
so take Katase-san with you.
Got it! We'll go find it.
General Affairs Office
No Unauthorized Personnel Allowed
Did you find it?
It's not over here.
If it's from over 30 years ago,
would it really...
Did you find it?
A Meowtaro pen case!
I had one of these! This is so nostalgic!
This place might be a treasure trove
to old-school Meowtaro fans!
Senpai, we should probably
finish looking before the sun sets.
I got a message from
the manager on the office chat.
Manager
It should be on one of the shelves in the back.
The back...
We've looked pretty much everywhere
up front, so let's head farther back.
Right.
Product Development
Group 2
What're you grinning about?
I feel like there's going to be
a large helping of sugar served up.
There's still so much stuff to look through.
Where do we even start?
Good question...
For now, I'll start lowering
the boxes on the upper shelves...
No one's here, right?
No one comes all the way down here.
Shinozaki-san, look over here.
But what if someone finds us?
We'll deal with that if it happens...
Public Relations
Ito Yuri
They're from PR. That's Ito-san and...
I guess.
Yeah.
Yoshida-san.
Public Relations
Yoshida Masao
What're they doing down here?
Could it be?!
Be what?
Th-Th-This might be...
What is it?
Masa-tan!
Yuri-tan!
Smooch!
Wha—?!
I knew it!
A-An office romance?!
Gosh, Masa-tan, you're so bad.
Only because you're so cute.
But we're working!
I was about to say!
I'd heard rumors, but... I didn't think...
Well, well, this is really something...
She's super staring!
I'm getting nervous being by the door...
Does the thought of getting found excite you?
Oh, you.
You've already been found, actually.
It's not that, but if we're going to
have fun, I wanna move to the back.
S-S-Senpai, they're coming this way!
I-I know! Wh-Where do we hide?
Yuri-tan.
Masa-tan.
Smooch!
Well, it's good that
we were able to hide, but....
Th-This really is really
cramped for two people.
It is. I have to say, those two...
Yuri-tan, Yuri-tan, oh, Yuri-tan!
How long are they going to
fool around like that?
Masa-tan, Masa-tan, oh, Masa-tan!
I hope they don't plan on
doing anything weird...
Yuri-tan Yuri-tan Yuri-tan!
No... I can't imagine
they would, in the office.
Masa-tan Masa-tan Masa-tan!
By the way... Senpai...
Well... sorry if I smell sweaty or anything...
It's okay.
Since it's you... I don't mind.
Wh-What does that mean?!
S-S-Senpai's ch-ch-chest...!
Sorry, Senpai...
It's okay, we're safe,
since I was able to catch...
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay!
I can't take more of this!
I need to get away soon...
Yuri-tan.
Somebody, chase those two off!
Masa-tan.
There has to be a way!
Senpai! The office chat!
What about it?
Use it to lure them away!
Basement
Come to the fifth floor.
Oh, crap!
Yay, yay!
Senpai, hurry and contact them!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Shinozaki-san...
When we hid in the locker before...
I put my phone in my back pocket.
Could you please get it?
O-Okay.
Sh-She's asking me to...
Reach around to h-her...
Butt...
My hands...
Can't reach.
Is it okay if I move some?
I'll be careful not to make any noise.
Okay.
Don't be embarrassed. Look at me.
Come on, if you touch me like that...
Not quite there...
Yuri-tan.
Masa-tan.
Masa-tan!
Yuri-tan!
Katase
Emergency!
Please come to the fifth floor!
Oh, crap!
Katase-san's calling us!
That's bad! We need to hurry
or she'll realize we've been slacking!
L-Looks like that worked.
Y-Yeah.
Nice to meet you!
I'm Meowtaro
Meow
Wait, is that...
The Meowtaro merchandise we were looking for!
All right!
I guess that's our silver lining!
Yeah!
W-We should hurry back, too.
R-Right.
Twinge!
I sense something... powerful.
Sorry?
Preciousness is detected
with one's sixth sense.
I don't think I'm gonna
be able to sleep tonight...
My Tiny Senpai.
What's round and soft?
I ended up not getting any sleep...
I didn't sleep at all last night.
My subordinates have been
acting weird since yesterday...
Could it be there's been
new developments of some kind?!
I didn't get much sleep, again...
Li'l bro. It seems there's something
new with you and Shiorin.
What are you doing here on
a workday, first thing in the morning?!
Manager-san
I sense lovey vibes between your brother
and Katase-san
Say... what? I must
confirm at once
Please do. I can handle things on
this end.
Please do!
Chihiro provided me with some updates.
Manager did that?! And why are you
sharing intel with my boss?!
Also, "Chihiro"?!
How close are you two anyway?!
Seriously, there's nothing
going on with Senpai.
Sniff, sniff, sniff...
What now?
I can smell Shiorin on your suit...
Wha?!
For her fragrance to be
so distinct on your clothing...
I must assume you two
were stuck together in a locker.
She's an ace detective!
Ugh...
I was trying to forget about it,
but now because of her...
It's in my head again.
I still feel so anxious...
maybe I should just...
Product Development
Group 2
Today I... I'm gonna...
Shinozaki-san?
Yes?!
There's been a delivery. Would you mind
accompanying me to general affairs?
S-Sure.
Is something wrong?
N-No.
Senpai's not acting any differently.
Maybe she just thinks of what
happened as a workplace accident.
But...
if there's a chance...
that she might feel the same way...
Senpai.
May I have some of your time after work?
There's something
I'd like to discuss privately.
Okay.
Man, Meowtaro is honestly so cute.
I know what you mean. The way
he's so floppy is weirdly addictive.
You can really see how he was able to be
the company's big attraction for 30 years.
He wants to talk privately...
I wonder what about?
Maybe...
maybe it's...
Shinozaki-san.
What did you want to discuss?
Senpai...
I love you! Please, go out with me!
Th-Th-That's a little too big of a jump!
I-I-It could be something else, like needing
advice about work or personal advice, right?!
But...
if it really is that...
I'd...
Oh, did you hear, Katase-san?
Yoshida-san from PR is getting reassigned.
Yoshida-san...?
He was apparently fooling around
with Ito-san while on the clock.
There were a ton of witnesses, too.
They were so into each other
they probably didn't notice.
I guess with office romances,
someone will need to get reassigned, huh?
I dunno. I think this is mostly
about it affecting their work.
Reassignment...
It's kind of a shock, though.
The way
they were
before
I always thought those two
were pretty cool and impressive.
All right, let's move on!
I've got it!
I've got your back!
But then...
The way
they are
now
Yuri-tan.
Masa-tan!
Yuri-tan...
That is such a thing. Guys who
change the second they get a girlfriend.
I know, right?
Is it really so common?
Oh, totally! They try to act cool
in front of their friends...
This? It's my chick.
Cute? I dunno. Isn't she average?
Or they try to white knight too hard.
Isn't he staring at you too much?
Next time he looks,
I think I'll let him have it.
Funnily enough, it's the serious,
down-to-earth types
who tend to go haywire
when they get a girlfriend.
And worst of all are the ones
who go infantile once they start dating.
Infantile?
I guess they want to be babied?
They want pats on the head and stuff.
Shenpai! Sweepy! Gib headpats!
Oh, if you insist. Good boy.
C-Cute...
I-I think that might be kind of nice...
Isn't it cute?
Come to think of it, you've always
had shotacon vibes, Katase-san.
I'm a... shota... shota... shota...
I'm a... shota...
What's your type, Hayakawa-san?
M-Me...?
Someone who does good work, who's kind,
has a good head on their shoulders
and is understanding of my hobbies,
and always looks out for me...
You're not gonna find a dreamboat like that
in reality. Come back down to Earth.
What a fun topic.
Ito-san?
It's true that women can make men change...
But!
Men can change women, too.
Yuri-tan!
So this is where you've been, Yuri-tan!
Masa-tan!
I'm so sorry for leaving you alone like that!
It's okay! Absence makes the heart grow fonder.
Isn't that right?!
Yes, it certainly is!
Yuri-tan.
Masa-tan.
Smoochie!
They've gone totally, completely...
...absolutely stupid.
Masa-tan!
Yuri-tan, I'll never let you go again!
Totally, completely... absolutely stupid.
Masa-tan, hold me tight!
That display in there
was a little too spicy for me.
Is that what would happen?
Acting like that...
I'm so sorry I left you alone!
It's okay! Absence makes the heart grow fonder!
Isn't that right?
Yeah! You're right!
Shiorin.
Takkun.
Squeeze!
Totally, completely... absolutely stupid.
I'm finally gonna tell Senpai...
I can't run away! I need to brace myself!
Shinozaki-san.
Senpai.
Let's always be good coworkers, okay?
Because I don't want to be totally,
completely, absolutely stupid.
I think having a relationship
that stays the same is wonderful.
Because being totally, completely,
absolutely stupid would be awful.
Sorry, I kind of talked over you there.
What did you want to discuss, Shinozaki-san?
I...
I was going to say the same thing!
That's great!
We're on the same wavelength.
We sure are.
I was really worried you were having
trouble with work or something!
Are you going home now?
Let's head to the station together.
Yeah, sure.
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar
Magical Girl
Shiorin
Magical Girl Shiorin!
Episode 1
Action! Shiorin
"Action! Shiorin"!
Big trouble, Shiorin!
What's wrong, Yutakappi?
Bad guys are attacking!
The Demon Lord has come to town!
Is that true?!
Come on, Shiorin!
Okay!
That's enough!
Stop this right now, Demon Lord!
Magical Girl Shiorin is here to face you!
So, you've come, Magical Girl...
I'm the new Demon Lord,
here to take over for my predecessor.
It's a pleasure to be working with you!
Thank you very much.
Right.
All right, here goes!
I'm Magical Girl Shiorin.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Oh, let me accept your card.
I'll probably need a while
to get used to everything, so...
It's only my third year doing this, so I know
that everyone has to start somewhere.
Right.
You can go ahead
and put the business card away.
R-Right...
I know the timing can be kind of awkward.
I appreciate your consideration.
Magical Girl
Shiorin
Magical Girl Shiorin!
"Disaster! Shiorin"!
Episode 25
Disaster! Shiorin
This is bad.
I'm so sorry, Professor Haya Kawa.
You won't be able to transform now.
With your transformation
compact in this state...
I was running and it fell out of my bag.
Like a cell phone?!
Da-ding!
Enemy attack!
At a time like this?!
Come on, Shiorin!
But...
We've got no choice.
It's older, but please, use it.
Th-That is...
There's no other way right now!
Stop right there!
So, you've come, Magical Giiiirl—
Wh-Wh-What happened to you?! What is that?!
There was a bit of an incident...
so I'm using an older model
of transformation compact...
The old days were hot!
Defeating you when you aren't
at your best would mean nothing.
I'll take my leave, for today.
Thank you so much.
I'm so, so sorry...
I suppose this might be a job for me,
as the previous Demon Lord...
To be continued!